Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President Records 1986-2000
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- 1994
  - I-N
    - Leadership Conference, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 375)
    - Libraries, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 376)
    - Miscellaneous "M", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 377)
    - Military Science, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 378)
    - Minority Affairs, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 379)
    - Multicultural Student Services, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 380)
    - Murrow Stamp Issue, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 381)
    - Murrow Symposium, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 382)
    - Music, Department of, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 383)
    - Miscellaneous "N", 1994 (Box 13, Folder 384)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), Jan.-Mar. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 385)
    - NCAA, Apr.-Jun. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 386)
    - NCAA, Jully-Sept. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 387)
    - NCAA, Oct.-Dec. 1994 (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - NCAA- President's Commission, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 389)
  - N-R
    - National Science Foundation, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 390)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), Jan.-Mar. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 391)
    - NASULGC, Apr.-June 1994 (Box 14, Folder 392)
    - NASULGC, July-Sept. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 393)
    - NASULGC, Oct.-Dec. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 394)
    - NASULGC- Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 395)
    - NASULGC- Commission on Information Technologies (1), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 396)
    - NASULGC- CIT (2), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 397)
    - News and Information, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 398)
    - News and Information (News Releases), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 399)
    - News and Information- Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 400)
    - Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 401)
    - Miscellaneous "O", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 402)
    - Miscellaneous "P", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 403)
    - Pac-10 Conference, Jan.-June 1994 (Box 14, Folder 404)
    - Pac-10 Conference, July-Dec. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 405)
    - Pac-10 Conference Handbook, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 406)
    - Parking, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 407)
    - Pharmacy, College of, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 408)
    - Physical Plant, Department of, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 409)
    - Plant Pathology, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 410)
    - President, House, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 411)
    - Professional Leaves, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 412)
    - Provost, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 413)
    - Publications, Office of, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 414)
    - Pullman, Chamber of Commerce, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 415)
    - Pullman, City of, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 416)
    - Miscellaneous "Q", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 417)
    - Questionnaires, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 418)
    - Miscellaneous "R", 1994 (Box 14, Folder 419)
    - Recommendations (A-M), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 420)
    - Recommendations (N-Z), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 421)
    - Registrar, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 422)
    - Residence Life and Housing, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 423)
  - R-S
    - Report of the NCAA Special Committee to Study a Division I-A Football - Championship (1), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 424)
    - Report of the NCAA Special Committee to Study a Division I-A Football - NCAA Report (2), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 425)
    - Retirements, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 426)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 427)
    - Russia, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 428)
    - Miscellaneous "S", 1994 (Box 15, Folder 429)
    - Safety Division, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 430)
    - Scholarships, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 431)
    - Seafirst, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 432)
    - Small Business Development Center, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 433)
    - Spokane Intercollegiate Research and Technology Institute, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 434)
    - Spokane, City of, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 435)
    - Spokane, Symphony, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 436)
    - Spokane, Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 437)
    - Spokane, Unlimited, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 438)
    - Staff Senate, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 439)
    - State: Attorney General, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 440)
    - State: Auditor, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 441)
    - State: Combined Fund Drive, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 442)
    - State: General Administration, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 443)
    - State: Governor, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 444)
    - State: Higher Education Coordinating Board, Jan.-Feb. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 445)
    - State: HECB, Mar.-Apr. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 446)
    - State: HECB, May, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 447)
    - State: HECB, June, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 448)
    - State: HECB, July-Sept. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 449)
    - State: HECB, Oct. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 450)
    - State: HECB, Nov. 1993 (Box 15, Folder 451)
    - State: HECB, Dec. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 452)
  - S-Z
    - State: Liquor Control Board, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 453)
    - State: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 454)
    - State: Office of Fiscal Management, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 455)
    - State: Senators and Representatives, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 456)
    - Strategic Planning, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 457)
    - Student Affairs, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 458)
    - Miscellaneous "T", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 459)
    - Thank You, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 460)
    - Track, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 461)
    - Tribal File, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 462)
    - Tri-Cities: Technology Commercialization Task Force, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 463)
    - Trend Letter, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 464)
    - Miscellaneous "V", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 465)
    - US Bank, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 466)
    - US West, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 467)
    - U.S. Advisory Council on National Information Infrastructure, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - United States: Agriculture, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 469)
    - United States: Defense, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 470)
    - United States: Education, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 471)
    - United States: Energy, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 472)
    - United States: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 473)
    - United States: Senators and Representatives, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 474)
    - Universities and Colleges: Central, Eastern, Evergreen, Western, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 475)
    - Universities and Colleges: Idaho, University of, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 476)
    - Universities and Colleges: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 477)
    - Universities and Colleges: State Community Colleges, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 478)
    - Universities and Colleges: Washington, University of, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 479)
    - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 480)
    - Miscellaneous "V", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 481)
    - Volleyball, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 482)
    - Miscellaneous "W", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 483)
    - Washington Agriculture and Forestry Leadership, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 484)
    - Washington State China Relations Council, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 485)
    - Washington Council for International Trade, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 486)
    - Washington School Employees Credit Union, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 487)
    - Washington Water Power, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 488)
    - Western Cooperative, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 489)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 490)
    - Women, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 491)
    - Women's Resource and Research Center, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 492)
    - WSU: Spokane, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 493)
    - WSU: Tri-Cities, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 494)
    - WSU: Vancouver, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 495)
    - WSU: West, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 496)
    - Miscellaneous "Y", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 497)
    - Miscellaneous "Z", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 498)
  - PINKS
    - January Pinks (1), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 499)
    - January Pinks (2), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 500)
    - February Pinks (1), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 501)
    - February Pinks (2), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 502)
    - March Pinks, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 503)
    - April Pinks, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 504)
    - May Pinks (1), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 505)
    - May Pinks (2), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 506)
    - June Pinks (1), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 507)
    - June Pinks (2), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 508)
    - July Pinks, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 509)
    - August Pinks, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 510)
    - September Pinks, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 511)
- 1996 PINKS
  - January Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 515)
  - January Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 516)
  - Pinks February, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 517)
  - March Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 518)
  - March Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 519)
  - April Pinks (1-15), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 520)
  - April Pinks (16-30), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - May Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 522)
  - May Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 523)
  - June Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 524)
  - June Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 525)
  - July Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 526)
  - July Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 527)
  - August Pinks, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 528)
  - September Pinks, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 529)
  - October Pinks, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 530)
  - November Pinks (1), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 531)
  - November Pinks (2), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 532)
  - December Pinks (1-15), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 533)
  - December Pinks (16-31), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 534)
- Archives- Regents
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 535)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 537)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 539)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 541)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 542)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 543)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 546)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 548)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, Jan.-Mar. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 549)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, Apr.-June 1990 (Box 20, Folder 550)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, July-Aug. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 551)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, Sept. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 552)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, Oct. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 553)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, Nov.-Dec. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 554)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 555)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 556)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 557)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 558)
  - Regents Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 559)
  - Regents- Professional Leaves, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 560)
  - Regents- Correspondence, 1991, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 561)
  - Bill Wiley Memorial, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 562)
- 1995-1998 Smith's Committees
  - America's Public Television Stations- Board of Trustees Meeting (Washington, D.C.), March 22, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 563)
  - APTS- Grassroots Action Handbook, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 564)
  - APTS- Board of Trustees- Annual Retreat (Colorado Springs, Colorado), Oct. 1-4, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 565)
  - APTS Miscellaneous, Jan.-June 1998 (Box 21, Folder 566)
  - APTS Miscellaneous, July-Dec. 1998 (Box 21, Folder 567)
  - APTS Reimbursements and Forms, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 568)
  - Battelle: Laboratory Advisory Board, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 569)
  - Battelle: Institutional Plans, 1993-2002 (Box 21, Folder 570)
  - Forward Washington (folder empty), no date (Box 21, Folder 571)
  - NASULGC- Kellogg Commission, Jan.-Apr. 1998 (Box 21, Folder 572)
  - NASULGC- Kellogg Commission, May, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 573)
  - NCAA Division I- Board of Directors, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 574)
  - NCAA Executive Committee (1), 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 575)
  - NCAA Executive Committee (2), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 576)
  - NCAA Executive committee (3), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 577)
  - NCAA: Baseball Bat Issue, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 578)
  - Seattle Times- Board of Directors (1), 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 579)
  - Seattle Times- Board of Directors (2), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 580)
  - Spirit of 2000, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 581)
  - Technology Alliance, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 582)
  - Tri-Cities Commercialization Partnership Executive Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 583)
- 1995-1998 Smith's Committees and Calendars
  - WA School Employees Credit Union, 1996 (Box 22-23, Folder 584)
  - Western Governors University (1), 1997-1998 (Box 22-23, Folder 585)
  - Western Governors University (2), 1998 (Box 22-23, Folder 586)
  - Calendar for 1988 (1), Jan.-June 1988 (Box 22-23, Folder 587)
  - Calendar for 1988 (2), July-Dec. 1988 (Box 22-23, Folder 588)
  - Calendar for 1989 (1), Jan.-June 1989 (Box 22-23, Folder 589)
  - Calendar for 1989 (2), July-Dec. 1989 (Box 22-23, Folder 590)
  - Calendar for 1990 (Box 22-23, Folder 591)
  - Calendar for 1991 (Box 22-23, Folder 592)
  - Calendar for 1992 (Box 22-23, Folder 593)
  - Calendar for 1993 (Box 22-23, Folder 594)
  - Calendar for 1994 (Box 22-23, Folder 595)
  - Calendar for 1995 (1), Jan.-June 1995 (Box 22-23, Folder 596)
  - Calendar for 1995 (2), July-Dec. 1995 (Box 22-23, Folder 597)
  - Calendar for 1996 (1), Jan.-June 1996 (Box 22-23, Folder 598)
  - Calendar for 1996 (2), July-Dec. 1996 (Box 22-23, Folder 599)
  - Calendar for 1997 (1), Jan.-June 1997 (Box 22-23, Folder 600)
  - Calendar for 1997 (2), July-Dec. 1997 (Box 22-23, Folder 601)
  - Calendar for 1998 (1), Jan.-June 1998 (Box 22-23, Folder 602)
  - Calendar for 1998 (2), July-Dec. 1998 (Box 22-23, Folder 603)
  - Calendar for 1999 (1), Jan.-June 1999 (Box 22-23, Folder 604)
- Unlabeled Box - Smith's Calendars
  - Calendar for 1999 (2), July-Dec. 1999 (Box 24, Folder 605)
  - Calendar for 2000, Jan.-June 2000 (Box 24, Folder 606)
  - Aerial Photograph of the Riverpoint Higher Education Park (in frame), April 19, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 607)
  - Consortium For International Development- Silver Anniversary (1967-1992)- CID (Box 24, Folder 608)
  - President's State of the University Address- Dr. Samuel Smith- Washington State University, October 19, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 608)
  - President's State of the University Address- Dr. Samuel Smith- Washington State University, Sept. 15, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 608)